some traditions are weird I like the
tradition of serving drinks to people on
airplanes I fly that's nice but what
about the people on the bus cuz if
you're on the bus things are not going
well you could use a
drink give that man a drink he's on
Greyhound
oh I took Greyhound a few times in the
old days it's just a bunch of people
that don't have a car or a friend with a
car Scouts from the Springer Show we
there looking for
talent the bus is so slow and they have
the G name it after a racing dog this
bus should be called crippled
poodle chihuahua with
rickets maybe the strangest tradition in
all of American culture the retirement
party really you're giving me a gold
watch today the first day of my whole
life that I I don't care what time it
is I'm never going to look at a watch
again watch me trade this in for a
hammock I would love to be retired
that's something an old guy says right
I'm looking forward to it now here's how
I know I'm getting older now when I see
a beautiful teenage girl I think to
myself wow I bet she's got a hot
[Music]
mom it's funny I want to see the mother
now I didn't know that was the next
phase of life does that continue
eventually I'm like where's granny all
right I want to see three generations of
this magic let's
go trying to eat better now that I'm
growing up you enjoying the rice cakes
as much as I
am why do they come with a twist tie are
they worried they're going to go
stale
these are terrible yes they're
fresh a price cake it's it tastes like a
styr like you punched a circle out of a
styrofoam cooler or something first time
I had rice cakes I thought there was a
mix up at the factory well obviously
these are the packing materials that the
cakes usually come
in keep them moist and
delicious how do you screw up rice and
Cake those are both good things rice
pudding Is Awesome carrot cake fantastic
rice cake kill yourself a urinal cake is
better than a race
cake at least then you have low
expectations you'll be
fine hey guys watch my entire special
for 99 cents all you got to do is click
here you can also watch more Clips
that's a clickable thing and you can
also subscribe another click you're on
the internet everyone's clicking all the
the time click it already click click do
it click